fxoptimax.com 2016-03-05

# FXOptimax Privacy Policy - FXOptimax

### Privacy Policy

FXOptimax sets the highest standards in respect to our clients, partners or any other counterparties' privacy. Under no circumstances, unless under court decision or legal request, can the data be disclosed.

## Protection

All client data are protected by an SSL-encrypted connection to our Personal Area at secure.fxoptimax.com. It is highly unlikely that this encryption will be broken by any third party.

## Personal Information

When you open a real account, certain personal information is required. This information allows us to estimate your financial needs, process your requests and transactions, and keep you informed about our upcoming products and services.

Required information may include: full name, address and birth date. We require confirmation of your identity, as set forth in the Customer Agreement. This includes passport or driver's license, or any other ID and proof of residential address.

Anti-Money Laundering ("AML") regulations require financial institutions to collect information and take action where necessary, in order to verify a customer's identity.

## Cookies

We use a technology called "cookies", which enables us to provide you with a better experience in using our website by sending small text files from our servers to your computer. These cookies do not track your private information.

## Affiliates

We may share some or all of the personal information described above with our affiliates in order to service client accounts or inform clients of new products and services. Our affiliates may include companies controlled or owned by us, as well as companies which have an ownership interest in our company. Our affiliates maintain the privacy of your information in the same manner and to the same extent as we do, and in accordance with this privacy policy.

## Third Parties

We do not disclose your personal information to third parties, except as described in this privacy policy. Third party disclosures may include sharing such information with non-affiliated companies that perform support services for your account.

## Regulators

Disclosure of your personal information might be necessary in order to comply with applicable laws and regulations. This may include disclosing personal information in order to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies, as may be necessary to protect our property or rights.

## Payment Information

We do not keep nor store, in any form, customer payment information.
